Guide to the Advocate Research and Education Foundation/Advocate Experience Records, 1978-1981
Advocate Research and Education Foundation/Advocate Experience Records, 1978-1981
- Series III. Advocate Experience Facilitator Information Sheets [ RESTRICTED]
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 27-28 Jun. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 8-9 Aug. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
  - Advocate Experience Intensive Los Angeles - n.d. [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 19-20 Sept. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 24-25 Oct. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
  - Advocate Experience Intensive Los Angeles - n.d. [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 28-29)
  - Miscellaneous Facilitator Information Sheets [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 30-32)
- Series IV. Advocate Experience Audio and Video Cassettes and Slides
  - Sixteen videotapes pertaining to the Advocate Experience, including training sessions, graduates sharing the experience, and David B. Goodstein presentations (Box 13)
  - Twenty audiocassettes pertaining to the Advocate Experience, including seminar sessions, Opening Space session, disco music, and "Ethel Merman Single" (Box 13)
  - Approximately 90 slides pertaining to the Advocate Experience (Box 13)